memecollection.net 2017-12-17

# Privacy Policy - Meme Collection

**Personal Information**

As with most other websites, we collect the data you provide to us when you visit or post a comment to our site. This information may include your name, your email address, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Chrome, Safari or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. Your personal information will never be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside memecollection.net.

 **Cookies**

We also use third party advertisements on MemeCollection.net to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web  
beacons when they advertise on our site. Google, through their Adsense Program, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to memecollection.net users based on their visit to this and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

 **Third Party Companies**

Third party companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [Click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

 **Facebook:**  As a registered Facebook user, you are also subject to Facebook’s privacy policy. Please check your Facebook account privacy settings for further information. When you first access the App, you will be presented with a Facebook permissions page, which will advise you about the Facebook information you will be sharing with the App and other Facebook users. You can then decide whether or not to share your Facebook information by using the App. If you decide not to grant permission you will not be able to use the App. By granting permission you will be agreeing to share your Facebook user details (including your name, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID and any other information you choose to share according to your Facebook account settings) as well as the user details of your Facebook friends, and information about your use of the App, for example, the articles you are reading. If you choose to post content or other data on the App, for example, by commenting on an article, this can be accessed by all of your Facebook friends. If you decide not to share information with your Facebook friends about a particular article you have accessed you can make your reading private using the “remove from timeline” facility at the top of the article page. To unsubscribe go to our Facebook page and at the top of the article page and select “Remove this application”. Alternatively, remove the App by accessing the application settings in your Facebook account settings. Once you remove the App we no longer have permission to access your Facebook information and your data will be removed from the App.

“This blog is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with, Facebook”

All images on memecollection are readily available in various places on the Internet and believed to be in public domain. Majority of our images are user-submitted and we cannot confirm their source.  
If you believe that any content appearing on memecollection infringes on your copyright, please let us know. E-mail us at admin@memecollection.net. The infringing material will be removed as soon as possible. There are thousands of images on memecollection, please make sure you include the URL of the specific image.
